迈克 · 诺斯: 这可能是我将要做的最有价值的事情之一
&gt;&gt; Mike North: This is probably one of
the most valuable things that I'm going to
在这个工作室里教你们
teach you in this workshop, and
这是一个从 JavaScript 转换到 TypeScript 的秘诀。
it is a recipe for
converting from JavaScript to TypeScript.
所以，打字稿最大的优点之一就是它可以
So one of the great things
about TypeScript is it can
非常非常容易地与 JavaScript 进行互操作。
inter-operate with JavaScript very,
very easily.
你将会有 JS 和 TS 模块并排。
You're gonna have JS and
TS modules side by side.
你可以导入一个方向或者另一个方向，一切都会好起来。
You can import in one direction or
the other and everything will be okay.
并不是很多编程语言都能给你这个。
Not a lot of programming
languages give you this.
所以我们不应该将 JavaScript 转换为 TypeScript
So we shouldn't treat a transition
from JavaScript to TypeScript
同样的代码库更改，将导致更改
as the same kind of change to a code
base that would result from a change
把一种编程语言和一些完全不相关的东西联系起来。
in one programming language to
something totally unrelated.
这就像重写一些东西从 Ruby 到 Rust。
It's like rewriting
something from Ruby to Rust.
这就像苹果和桔子一样，对吗？
That is like apples and oranges, right?
所以我要给你们讲一个三步骤的过程，这个过程会让你们明白
So I'm gonna lead you down a three-step
process that will make it so
这个更改可以一次对几个文件进行递增更改。
this change can be made incrementally
on a couple of files at a time.
或者在多次传递中到达您正在寻找的端点
Or in multiple passes where you get
to the endpoint you are looking
这样就不会有潜在的额外工作了
to get without potentially running
into creating extra work for
你自己或者对那些依赖这些代码的人的破坏。
yourself or disruption for
people who depend on that code.
首先，让我们讨论一下什么是不该做的。
First, let's talk about what not to do.
你不想做的是混合从 JavaScript 到
What you don't want to do is mix
a conversion from JavaScript to
功能上的变化，这些变化可能很微妙。
TypeScript with functional changes,
and these can be subtle.
这可能是检查
It can be the difference
between checking whether
一个值对于一种支票来说是否真实，对吗？
a value is truthy or
not to a type of check, right?
这是真值还是检查这个值是否未定义，没有零和
Is this truth versus check whether
this value is undefined, no zero and
空字符串会有不同的处理方式。
empty string are gonna
be handled differently.
因此，如果可能的话，你应该尽量避免这些功能上的改变。
So you want to avoid even those kinds
of functional changes if you can.
如果您的测试覆盖率是，那么您不希望尝试这种转换
You don't want to try this kind of
conversion if your test coverage is
真的很低。
really low.
因为在我们的三个步骤中的每一步之后，都要运行一个测试扫描，就像您的测试扫描一样
Because after each of our three steps run
a test sweep like your test sweep for
这段代码，并确保我们不仅已经转换为打字稿,
this piece of code, and ensure that not
only have we converted to TypeScript,
但是图书馆还是按照我们的方式运作。
but the library still works
the way we want it to work.
迈克 · 诺斯: 你不想让完美成为优秀的敌人。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: You don't want to let
the perfect be the enemy of the good.
从这个意义上来说，我的意思是不要试图把事情打得太强烈，太早。
And in this sense what I mean is don't try
to type things too strongly, too early on.
你的目标是得到转变，你会开始看到一些强大的好处
Your goal is to get converted, and you'll
start to see some benefits of the strong
打字，但是不要过早地打字来追求这些好处。
typing, but don't chase those benefits
by trying to type things up prematurely.
你想被转换过来，然后
You want to get converted over and
然后开始在有意义的地方加强打字。
then start applying stronger
typing where things make sense.
这样做的原因是，特别是如果您一次转换几个文件，并且
The reason for this is, particularly if
you convert a few files at a time, and
你有一些非常强类型的东西。
you have some very strongly typed things.
一旦你转换一些其他的文件，交互与您的已经
As soon as you convert some of the other
files that interact with your already
强代码，你没有机会开始排序弱类型。
strong code, you don't have a chance
to start out with sort of weak types.
因为你的约束已经很紧了，对吧？
Cuz your constraints
are already very tight, right?
在你的应用程序的一个部分。
In one part of your app.
所以你应该记住目标是,
So you kind of want to
remember the goal is,
改变信仰，然后我们再把事情闹大。
get converted and
then we'll ratchet things up.
不要忘记为类型添加测试。
Don't forget to add tests for your types.
同样，dts lint 是您编写测试的特定方式
Again, dts lint is the way you write
tests that's specifically are for
只提供类型资料。
type information only.
特别是对于图书馆，不要试图发布
And also particularly for libraries,
don't try to publish types for
直到你满意为止。
consumer use until you're happy with them.
因为人们将随库一起出现的类型信息作为
Because people take type information
that comes along with the library as
公共空气污染指数的指示。
an indication of a public API.
你应该做什么，不应该做什么。
What you should do and what you shouldn't.
记住，这是开发者的意图。
Remember, it's developer intent.
如果你一开始就用打字稿写了这段代码,
If you wrote this code in
TypeScript in the first place,
这些类型表示你能做什么和不能做什么的代码。
those types would express what you can
do and can't do with piece of code.
所以如果你过早地让人们使用这些东西，并且
So if you prematurely have
people using this stuff, and
到处都是放松的人，你可以带他们去野外
there's a bunch of looseness all over
the place, you can lead them on a wild
白费力气，他们认为事情应该是可行的和有效的。
goose chase where they're assuming
things should be doable and valid.
事实并非如此。
And in fact that's not the case.